Nancy W. Anderson Papers MS112
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1968 -- 1999; MS112.003; 13.2 Linear Feet
  - Lincoln Filene Center, reports, 1993; MS112.003.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Lincoln Filene Center (1 of 2), 1987 -- 1993; MS112.003.008.00032 (Box 8)
    forms, brochures, courses
  - Lincoln Filene Center (2 of 2), 1987 -- 1993; MS112.003.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, leadership institute, 1990; MS112.003.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Local action training, 1977 -- 1979; MS112.003.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Local FP2/wetlands bylaws, 1974; MS112.003.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - Lowell State Bridgewater (1 of 2), 1974; MS112.003.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Lowell State Bridgewater (2 of 2), 1974; MS112.003.008.00038 (Box 8)
  - MACC environmental education task force, 1973; MS112.003.008.00039 (Box 8)
  - MACC Nancy's history, 1969 -- 1981; MS112.003.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - MACC Newsletter, 1971 -- 1974; MS112.003.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - MACC Newsletter, 1975 -- 1978; MS112.003.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - MACC unlabeld publication file, 1978 -- 1982; MS112.003.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - MACC non-newsletters, 1979 -- 1987; MS112.003.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - MACC (1 of 2), 1984 -- 1989; MS112.003.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - MACC (2 of 2), 1984 -- 1989; MS112.003.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - MACC letters, misc., 1968 -- 1993; MS112.003.009.00008 (Box 9)
    Includes letters that address other topics
  - MACDC, 1992; MS112.003.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Maine Nuclear, 1995 -- 1996; MS112.003.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Maine Yankee, 1997; MS112.003.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Massachusetts Soviet trade council, 1990; MS112.003.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - MBTA, 1974; MS112.003.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - MBTA study by Tufts students, 1973; MS112.003.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - McGregor, Gregor, 1986 -- 1991; MS112.003.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - MDC watershed plan, 1993; MS112.003.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Mead, Molly, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Media, "How to use the media effectively", 1991; MS112.003.009.00018 (Box 9)
    Includes bibliography "Citizen action and social change"
  - Meeting agendas, 1975; MS112.003.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Meridian international seminar, 1993; MS112.003.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Mount Ida College, 1992; MS112.003.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Murphy, Alana, 1991 -- 1992; MS112.003.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Murphy, Evelyn, 1973 -- 1990; MS112.003.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - MWRA, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - NAAEE, 1993; MS112.003.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Nairobi, 1987; MS112.003.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Naples institute, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - National legislation, 1995; MS112.003.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - National Park Service, 1993; MS112.003.009.00029 (Box 9)
    May 3-5. Includes Talloires information
  - NEEC workshop material, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - NEEC packet conference agendas, 1993; MS112.003.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - NEEC workshop leaders' summaries, 1993; MS112.003.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - NEEC, 1994; MS112.003.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - New England environmental expo, 1989; MS112.003.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - NEEN project reports (1 of 2), 1978 -- 1979; MS112.003.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - NEEN project reports (2 of 2), 1978 -- 1979; MS112.003.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - NEEN conferences (NEEC) (1 of 2), 1979 -- 1990; MS112.003.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - NEEN conferences (NEEC) (2 of 2), 1979 -- 1990; MS112.003.009.00038 (Box 9)
    Includes photos 1991
  - NEEN newsletters, 1979 -- 1995; MS112.003.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - NEEN history, 1981; MS112.003.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - NEEN misc conference newpaer articles, 1981 -- 1987; MS112.003.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - NEEN correspodnece Simons, Caroline, 1995; MS112.003.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - NEEN, 1996; MS112.003.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - NEEN workshop, MS112.003.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - NEEN, "Networking as an eduction tool", MS112.003.009.00045 (Box 9)
    Nancy W. Anderson paper. No Date Available
  - NEES program directors' meeting, 1993; MS112.003.009.00046 (Box 9)
    April 30-May 1
  - NESEA, 1993; MS112.003.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - NESEA 5th annual, 1993; MS112.003.009.00048 (Box 9)
    October 21-23
  - New England Biolabs Foundation, 1992; MS112.003.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - New England Governor's Conference, 1989; MS112.003.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - New England Governor's Conference, 1992; MS112.003.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - New England Environmental Leadership Project, 1978; MS112.003.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - New England North East Environmental Studies Program directory, 1989; MS112.003.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - NIRS nuclear information, 1993; MS112.003.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Nuclear, 1993 -- 1994; MS112.003.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1989; MS112.003.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Nuclear resolution, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Oyster River High School, 1993; MS112.003.010.00010 (Box 10)
    February 9
  - Pesticide dilemma, forum proceedings, 1984; MS112.003.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Popova, Lydia, 1991 -- 1992; MS112.003.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Personnel, 1993; MS112.003.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Peterson, Russell, 1993; MS112.003.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Pilgrim, Hugh, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Polese, Clancy, 1991; MS112.003.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Population, MS112.003.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - President's Conference, 1995 -- 1996; MS112.003.010.00018 (Box 10)
    newsletters
  - President's Council, current, 1995 -- 1996; MS112.003.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - President's Task Force, 1994 -- 1995; MS112.003.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Press conferences, 1988; MS112.003.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Program director position, 1993; MS112.003.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Public Dialogue, Linkage, and Education, 1994 -- 1995; MS112.003.010.00023 (Box 10)
    President's Council Task Force Report, and other material
  - Reading conservation, 1971 -- 1972; MS112.003.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Reading conservation, 1975 -- 1977; MS112.003.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Reading open land trust, 1974 -- 1994; MS112.003.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Reading - roads, planning board, 1975 -- 1983; MS112.003.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Recommendations, 1993; MS112.003.010.00028 (Box 10)
    re: McManus, Thomas
  - Renew America, Searching for Success, 1991 -- 1993; MS112.003.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Rio, 1993; MS112.003.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - Rio summary, 1992; MS112.003.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Safe Energy, 1993; MS112.003.010.00032 (Box 10)
    October 24
  - Save the Harbor/Save the Bay, 1993; MS112.003.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Sears Island, 1995; MS112.003.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Secretary position, 1991; MS112.003.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - Senior College, USM, 1996; MS112.003.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - Sierra Club, 1996; MS112.003.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - Society of environmental journalists, 1993; MS112.003.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - Solar, MS112.003.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Assorted addresses by Nancy, 1986 -- 1989; MS112.003.010.00040 (Box 10)
    Addresses filed by Nancy Anderson
  - Speeches - Assorted un-filed speeches, MS112.003.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - AAUW address, 1989; MS112.003.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Air polution and acid rain, MS112.003.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Bentley College, 1989; MS112.003.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - China address, 1985; MS112.003.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Coastal speech Maine, 1992; MS112.003.010.00046 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - College Digest, 1990; MS112.003.010.00047 (Box 10)
    Article found filed with addresses
  - Speeches - Dukakis talk by Nancy, 1988; MS112.003.010.00048 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - EAEN September, 1990; MS112.003.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Environmental careers, MS112.003.010.00050 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Fletcher speech December, 1986; MS112.003.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Gallops Island, 1989; MS112.003.010.00052 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Ipswich River conference, 1980; MS112.003.010.00053 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Massachusetts Soviet Trade Council talk, 1990; MS112.003.010.00054 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - NEEC, 1992; MS112.003.010.00055 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - NEEN, 1988; MS112.003.010.00056 (Box 10)
  - Speeches - Oregon Island, 1986; MS112.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Speeches - Recycling ICMA, 1990; MS112.003.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Speeches - Russian and U.S. eighth graders, 1988; MS112.003.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Speeches - Smith College, 1991; MS112.003.011.00004 (Box 11)
    Friday January 25th 2:30 pm
  - Speeches - Talloires paper, 1993; MS112.003.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Speeches - Women's educational and industrial union publicity, 1990; MS112.003.011.00006 (Box 11)
    No speech text filed in folder
  - Stoneleigh-Burnam School, Greenfield MA, 1993; MS112.003.011.00007 (Box 11)
    February 15
  - Students guide to environmental programs, 1984 -- 1989; MS112.003.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Students guide to environmental programs, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Switzer, 1993; MS112.003.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - TEPC (Tufts Environmental Program Council), 1995; MS112.003.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Tides Foundation proposal (1 of 2), 1991 -- 1993; MS112.003.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Tides Foundation proposal (2 of 2), 1991 -- 1993; MS112.003.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Tufts New England Environmental Center proposal, 1984; MS112.003.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Tufts departments and committees, 1986 -- 1991; MS112.003.011.00015 (Box 11)
    Committee on research, education and policy
  - UEP department, 1992; MS112.003.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - UN Association Saturday, 1991; MS112.003.011.00017 (Box 11)
    December 7
  - UNCED 4th preparatory meeting, 1992; MS112.003.011.00018 (Box 11)
    March-April
  - UNCED (1 of 2), 1992; MS112.003.011.00019 (Box 11)
    June 1-12
  - UNCED (2 of 2), 1992; MS112.003.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - UNCED, 1991 -- 1992; MS112.003.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - UN Day, Hamilton, 1989; MS112.003.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - UNEP, 1989 -- 1991; MS112.003.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - Africa (1 of 2), 1991; MS112.003.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - Africa (2 of 2), 1991; MS112.003.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - Fellows, 1991 -- 1992; MS112.003.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - Fellows, 1992; MS112.003.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - Montreal protocol, 1992; MS112.003.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - Atchia, Michael, Africa, 1990 -- 1993; MS112.003.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - annual advisory selection meeting, 1993; MS112.003.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - UNEP - funding, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - United Nations of greater Boston, 1991; MS112.003.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1994 -- 1995; MS112.003.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - University of Southern Maine, 1993; MS112.003.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - University of Southern Maine, 1995 -- 1997; MS112.003.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - USAid proposal, 1992; MS112.003.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - Uxbridge High School Environment Conference, 1991; MS112.003.011.00037 (Box 11)
    November 23
  - Valdez Principles, 1989; MS112.003.011.00038 (Box 11)
    Includes speech by Nancy W. Anderson
  - Valdez Principles, 1992; MS112.003.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - Vidich, Charles, 1993; MS112.003.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - War (1 of 2), 1991; MS112.003.012.00001 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - War (2 of 2), 1991; MS112.003.012.00002 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Washington, Olympia (1 of 2), 1992; MS112.003.012.00003 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    October 20-21
  - Washington, Olympia (2 of 2), 1992; MS112.003.012.00004 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Washington (State), 1988; MS112.003.012.00005 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Wastewater advisory committee, 1993; MS112.003.012.00006 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    January
  - Wells, Maine, 1993; MS112.003.012.00007 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    March
  - Wet Light project, 1993; MS112.003.012.00008 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - WGBH, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.012.00009 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Wollman, Neil, 1993; MS112.003.012.00010 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Women's educational and industrial union, 1990; MS112.003.012.00011 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - World Affairs Council talk, 1989; MS112.003.012.00012 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - World Affairs Council, 1997; MS112.003.012.00013 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - World Paper, 1993; MS112.003.012.00014 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - WorldWIDE network, 1993; MS112.003.012.00015 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - WSCAC, 1993; MS112.003.012.00016 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - WSCAC (2), 1993; MS112.003.012.00017 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - WSCAC meeting, 1993; MS112.003.012.00018 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    May 18
  - Yale talk, 1992; MS112.003.012.00019 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    February 28
  - Yale University, 1993; MS112.003.012.00020 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Meridian International Center, 1993; MS112.003.015.00001 (Box 15)
    July
  - NAFTA-GATT, 1993; MS112.003.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1993; MS112.003.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - NEEC, 1994; MS112.003.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - NEEC, 1995; MS112.003.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - NEEN (1 of 3), 1975 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - NEEN (2 of 3), 1975 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - NEEN workshops, MS112.003.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - NEEV (New England Environmental Voters), 1993 -- 1995; MS112.003.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - New England River Basin Commission, 1974 -- 1975; MS112.003.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear (1 of 3), 1991 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear (2 of 3), 1991 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Nuclear (3 of 3), 1991 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - Population (1 of 2), 1993 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - Population (2 of 2), 1993 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Rhode Island School of Design, 1993; MS112.003.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Rio lecture, 1992; MS112.003.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Rukuba-Ngaiza, Nightingale, 1993; MS112.003.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Save the Harbor/Save the Bay, 1989 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - Seminars/events, 1994 -- 1995; MS112.003.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - Speeches, 1989 -- 1994; MS112.003.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Talloires, 1993; MS112.003.015.00024 (Box 15)
    June 10-12
  - Temelin, 1994; MS112.003.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - United Nations Association - Kennedy School, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.003.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - WSCAC (Water Supply Citizens Advisory Committee), 1994 -- 1996; MS112.003.015.00027 (Box 15)
- Correspondence, 1972 -- 1997; MS112.004; 3.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence of NWA as Director of Environmental Affairs and Senior Fellow at LFC, and as a Research Associate in the Fletcher School. When NWA filed or bound her correspondence, she often organized it in reverse chronological order, and bound and unbound correspondence usually overlapped chronologically and alphabetically. No attempt was made to interfile these. Un-filed letters were filed under "Miscellaneous Correspondence" (1975-1989).
  Correspondence also contains receipts, newspaper clippings, or other printed material.
  This series is arranged according to original order.
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1975 -- 1989; MS112.004.012.00021 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    Letters found un-filed
  - Correspondence - Environmental education task force, 1972; MS112.004.012.00022 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988; MS112.004.012.00023 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1989; MS112.004.012.00024 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1989; MS112.004.012.00025 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1989; MS112.004.012.00026 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1989; MS112.004.012.00027 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1989 -- 1990; MS112.004.012.00028 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    September - March
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1989 -- 1990; MS112.004.012.00029 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1989 -- 1990; MS112.004.012.00030 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1990; MS112.004.012.00031 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990; MS112.004.012.00032 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1990; MS112.004.012.00033 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
    April - September
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1990; MS112.004.012.00034 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1990; MS112.004.012.00035 (Box MS112 Shared 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1990; MS112.004.013.00001 (Box 13)
    September 11 - December 31
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1990; MS112.004.013.00002 (Box 13)
    September 11-December 31
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1990; MS112.004.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1991; MS112.004.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1991; MS112.004.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1991; MS112.004.013.00006 (Box 13)
    June-July
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1991; MS112.004.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1991; MS112.004.013.00008 (Box 13)
    August 1-November 21
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1991; MS112.004.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Assorted correspondence, 1988 -- 1991; MS112.004.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence - speakers, 1991 -- 1992; MS112.004.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, 1992; MS112.004.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1992; MS112.004.013.00013 (Box 13)
    March-July
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1992; MS112.004.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1992; MS112.004.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992; MS112.004.013.00016 (Box 13)
    August-November
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1992; MS112.004.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992 -- 1993; MS112.004.013.00018 (Box 13)
    December-January
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1992 -- 1993; MS112.004.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence NEEC speakers (1 of 2), 1992 -- 1993; MS112.004.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence NEEC speakers (2 of 2), 1992 -- 1993; MS112.004.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence NEEC workshops, 1992; MS112.004.013.00022 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1992; MS112.004.013.00023 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1992 -- 1993; MS112.004.014.00001 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993; MS112.004.014.00002 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    February
  - Correspondence, 1993; MS112.004.014.00003 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993; MS112.004.014.00004 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    April-June
  - Correspondence, 1993 -- 1994; MS112.004.014.00005 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    August-April
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1994; MS112.004.014.00006 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1994; MS112.004.014.00007 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence, 1993 -- 1994; MS112.004.014.00008 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1994 -- 1995; MS112.004.014.00009 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    June-May
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1994 -- 1995; MS112.004.014.00010 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence EAEN, Christopher Hormel (1 of 2), 1994 -- 1995; MS112.004.014.00011 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence EAEN, Christopher Hormel (2 of 2), 1994 -- 1995; MS112.004.014.00012 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence, 1994 -- 1995; MS112.004.014.00013 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    File created during processing
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1996; MS112.004.014.00014 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1996; MS112.004.014.00015 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence USM, 1996; MS112.004.014.00016 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1997; MS112.004.014.00017 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1997; MS112.004.014.00018 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
- Phone calls, 1988 -- 1993; MS112.005; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of phone call logs listing date and time of call, caller, and often content. Messages were presumably taken by an office assistant.
  - Phone calls, 1988; MS112.005.014.00019 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Phone calls (1 of 2), 1989; MS112.005.014.00020 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Phone calls (2 of 2), 1989; MS112.005.014.00021 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Phone calls, 1990; MS112.005.014.00022 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Phone calls (1 of 2), 1991 -- 1992; MS112.005.014.00023 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    May-February
  - Phone calls (2 of 2), 1991 -- 1992; MS112.005.014.00024 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
  - Phone calls, 1992; MS112.005.014.00025 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    March-November
  - Phone calls, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.005.014.00026 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    December-May
  - Phone calls, 1993; MS112.005.014.00027 (Box MS112 Shared 3)
    See Agenda 21 Subject file, box 3, item 00004
- Publications and press, 1940 -- 1995; MS112.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains assorted published material. Publications either were un-filed or filed under "P" in the original subject files.
  Sub-series 1, "NWA authored publications": This sub-series contains articles and pamphlets written by NWA (some of them un-filed) and includes the MACC newsletter which NWA edited for approximately 10 years. NWA usually filed articles and pamphlets in her subject files under "P" with overly broad file names such as "Publications," "Publicity," and "Articles." For ease of use, these were moved to the publication series during processing.
  Sub-series 2, "Publications about NWA": This sub-series contains newspaper and journal articles about NWA or for which she was interviewed, as well as publications for which she was consulted. Many of these folders were originally filed in the subject files under "Publicity."
  Sub-series 3, "Publications and press": This sub-series contains un-filed books, brochures, conference proceedings, flyers, journals, newsletters, position papers, and reports dealing with environmental topics and organizations. Publications and press material are also in subject files, e.g., filed under creating agency or appropriate environmental topic. Material filed in this way was left in its subject file. Users are advised to consult both the publication series as well as relevant subject files.
  This series is grouped into three sub-series.
  - Assorted small publications, MS112.006.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Camping Can Be Fun, 1957; MS112.006.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - How to Publish a Newsletter, MS112.006.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Ipswich River Dilemma, 1981; MS112.006.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - MACC Newsletters, 1973 -- 1979; MS112.006.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - MACC Newsletters, 1973 -- 1982; MS112.006.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - The Media, 1982; MS112.006.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - The Media: How to use it Effectively, 1978 -- 1991; MS112.006.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Nancy's article current, 1988 -- 1989; MS112.006.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Networking as an Educational Tool, 1992; MS112.006.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - New England Environmental Network News, 1978 -- 1984; MS112.006.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - New England Environmental Network News, 1985 -- 1989; MS112.006.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - New England Environmental Network News, 1990 -- 1993; MS112.006.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Notes on Public Hearings, MS112.006.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Volunteer Development, 1982; MS112.006.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Worldwide Responses to the Environmental Crisis, MS112.006.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Newspaper clippings on environmental issues, 1978 -- 1992; MS112.006.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Publicity - Articles featuring NWA, 1966 -- 1993; MS112.006.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Publicity - Articles featuring NWA, 1980 -- 1993; MS112.006.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Are You Concerned? Its Your Town of Reading, Conservation Commission, Town of Reading, Massachusetts, MS112.006.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Citizen Participation, 1983; MS112.006.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Coast Alert, Scientists Speak Out, by Daniel W. Anderson, et.al., 1981; MS112.006.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - EAEN Conference Proceedings, Nairobi, Kenya, 1992 -- 1993; MS112.006.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Final Draft: an environmental issue, arms control - partisan or non-partisan, by Major General W. T. Fairbourn, 1986; MS112.006.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Flyer, All-University Forum Series, Individual in Contemporary Society, 1983; MS112.006.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Forest and Park News, 1976; MS112.006.002.00026 (Box 2)